maxient.com 2015-02-19

# Privacy Policy « Maxient

## We respect your privacy.

This policy covers how Maxient treats personal information that is received, including your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. We collect information from your browser, including your IP addresses and the page you request. We might ask for your contact information when you correspond with us, call us to request service, register to attend a seminar, or participate in an online survey.

The site contains links to other sites at which personal information is collected. In such instances, unless expressly provided to the contrary, the collection and use of your personal information will be governed by the privacy policy applicable to that site.

Maxient does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested from us.

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person or otherwise required by law.

Note that we may update this policy without notifying you personally.

E-mail: [info@maxient.com](mailto:info@maxient.com)

## In their words….

“I have nothing but positive things to say about the company and the product! From the first day I spoke to a representative about their product until now, I have been impressed by their knowledge of student conduct processes, our need to track data for Clery reporting, and their responsiveness to the client. I couldn’t imagine a better partner for us than Maxient!”

_Dr. Kevin W. Bailey  
Assoc. Vice President for Student Affairs  
Tulane University_
